{
    "subject": "resource/Zookeeper_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Columbia_Pictures_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Zookeeper (film) is Category: Columbia Pictures films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9462574124336243,
            "question": "Is Zookeeper associated with Columbia Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8429251909255981,
            "question": "If someone likes films produced by Columbia Pictures, would they likely enjoy Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7963137030601501,
            "question": "What type of films are categorized under Columbia Pictures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7375310063362122,
            "question": "To what category does the film Zookeeper belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5027556419372559,
            "question": "Is Zookeeper a film released by a major studio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.465982049703598,
            "question": "What film studio produced Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4250490367412567,
            "question": "What is the production company behind the film Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42479032278060913,
            "question": "Can you name a film studio that produced Zookeeper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3868250548839569,
            "question": "Which category does Zookeeper fall into based on its production company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3010881245136261,
            "question": "Based on its production company, what genre might Zookeeper belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Zookeeper (film) is Category: Columbia Pictures films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6018_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which category does Zookeeper fall into based on its production company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6018_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film studio that produced Zookeeper?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6018_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the production company behind the film Zookeeper?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6018_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6018_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the film \"Zookeeper,\" including that it was released by Columbia Pictures, which supports the statement that the subject of \"Zookeeper\" falls under the category of Columbia Pictures films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}